# Franco Prandi

# Full Stack Developer



in Franco Prandi 🕝 Franco Prandi

My Website • CABA, Argentina

# **ABOUT ME**

I am a full-stack developer specialized in Front End web applications. I excel in collaborative environments, striving to foster a comfortable environment for teamwork. I place a strong emphasis on

empathy towards my teammates to facilitate project progression.

My goal is to bring my creativity, dedication and knowledge to IT teams. I am always willing to offer help and equally open to learning, with the goal of continuous professional growth.

### **EDUCATION**

# **Coding Bootcamp**

Plataforma 5 Code Academy 09/2023 - 12/2023

Training in full-stack development with Javascript, with more than 8 hours of programming per day, using PERN and MERN stacks. Theoretical-practical mode applying agile methodologies, pair programming and collaborative work methodologies (SCRUM).

## CourseIt

05/2022 - 07/2022

Frontend development course, in which we saw the basics of technologies such as HTML, CSS and Javascript, with a theoreticalpractical method.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Front End Developer

Fast Delivery

01/2024 - 03/2024

In a collaborative team using SCRUM methodology, I have contributed to the development of the Front End of a logistics application for a company with hundreds of delivery drivers. The technologies used includes React, Next.js and Typescript, along with CSS for styles and axios for communication with the server.

The app allows delivery drivers to register, log in and select the packages they will deliver on a daily basis. It also provides the company with a view to monitor the operation, visualizing the packages assigned to each delivery person and their corresponding statuses.

### Front End Developer

Mi Turno Web App

11/2023 - 12/2023

It was a group project, in which I was in charge of a part of the frontend, including technologies such as React, Next.js and libraries such as Material UI, Axios, dayjs. We used the SCRUM collaborative work methodology.

It is a web application that facilitates the booking of appointments for companies with physical branches. The system allows to manage the flow of customers in each branch and customize the number of simultaneous customers per branch and define ranges schedules and duration of shifts.

## **Full Stack Developer**

**TMDB** 

10/2023 - 11/2023

It was an individual project, in which I was in charge of the backend, using technologies such as Express, cors, cookieparser, jwt, pg, sequelize. And also the frontend, in which I included React, react-dom, libraries like bulma, bootstrap and css for its design.

This is a website that presents a collection of movies and TV series, each accompanied by detailed information and their respective trailers. Customers can create personalized profiles, allowing them to easily browse and search for content by name. In addition, the site includes sections showcasing trending movies and series.



# SKILLS

HTML5 | CSS3 | Javascript | Typescript | React | Next.js | Node.js | Express.js | PostgreSQL | Sequelize | Git | Material UI | Bootstrap | Bulma | Scrum | Tailwind CSS



# LANGUAGES

**English** — C1 | **Portuguese** — B1